Guide to the Arden B. Schell Watergate Collection, 1972-1974
George Mason University Libraries
- Arden B. Schell Watergate collection, 1972-1974
  - Impeachment Inquiry--general correspondence, 93rd Congress, 1972-1974 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    10.9 (Impeachment)
  - Memoranda: William P. Dixon to "Congressman", 1972-1974 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    10.10 William P. Dixon
  - Memoranda: CIA, Department of Justice, FBI re: Watergate, 1972-1974 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    10.11 Central Intelligence Agency (CIA); Department of Justice; Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI); Watergate Hotel
  - Notes, 1972-1974 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    10.
  - Materials relating to Watergate and impeachment investigation, 1972-1974 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    10.13 (Impeachment)
  - Watergate Chronology: A Compendium of Scandal and Revelations, 1972-1974 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    10.14 (Watergate chronology)
  - Watergate indictments, 1972-1974 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    10.15
  - Background information--White House Staff and President Nixon's Campaign Organizations, May 9, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    10.16 Richard M. Nixon (campaign organizations); White House staff
  - Summary of Facts Supporting Conclusion that President Willfully Evaded Portion of Income Taxes for Years 1969 through 1972, 1972-1974 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    11.1 Richard M. Nixon (income taxes)
  - Senate Select Committee Report--Purchase of Earrings for Mrs. Nixon, 1972-1974 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    11.2 Patricia Nixon (gifts); Harry Winston
  - Impeachment Inquiry--Report on Impoundment of Funds, June 12, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    11.3 (Impeachment)
  - Expenditure of Federal Funds in Support of Presidential Properties, 1972-1974 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    11.4 (Camp David, Maryland; Key Biscayne, Florida; San Clemente, California)
  - Report on Government Expenditures Made on President Nixon's Private Properties at San Clemente and Key Biscayne, 1972-1974 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    11.5 (Impeachment; Key Biscayne, Florida; San Clemente, California)
  - Henry Kissinger testimony, memoranda, and nomination hearings before the Senate Committee on Foreign Relations, 1972-1974 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    11.6 (Cambodia; Vietnam; wiretapping); Henry Kissinger; National Security Council
  - The Huston Plan, 1972-1974 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    11.7 (Huston Plan); Central Intelligence Agency (CIA); Richard Helms; J. Edgar Hoover
  - Wiretapping, 1972-1974 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    11.8 Joseph Kraft; Donald Nixon
  - Milk Fund (miscellaneous), 1972-1974 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    11.9 (Milk--Price supports for)
  - Materials relating to the bombing of Cambodia, 1972-1974 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    11.10 (Cambodia; Impeachment)
  - Materials relating to the International Telephone and Telegraph investigation, 1972-1974 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    11.11 International Telephone and Telegraph (ITT); Leon Jaworski; J.J. Pickle (US Representative)
  - Memorandum with Facts/Bases Underlying Proposed Subpoena for Presidential Conversations Necessary for Committees Inquiry into Watergate and Aftermath, 1972-1974 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    11.12 (Watergate investigation)
  - Materials Respecting Proposed Article III, Failure to Comply with Subpoenas, 1972-1974 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    11.13 (Impeachment; Transcripts of White House tapes); Richard M. Nixon (subpoenas)
  - Various impeachment inquiries and exhibits, 1972-1974 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    11.14 (Impeachment)